Like Diane said, before you run your experiment you'll need to decide how
像 Diane 所说的 在进行实验之前
many page views you plan to collect before you make your conclusion.
你需要决定采集多少页面浏览量 以得出结论
First let's look at how the distribution changes when you increase
首先来看看你增加样本量时
the sample size.
分布会有什么变化
This is what the distribution of results would look like if you collected
如果你采集 1000 个样本 结果就会是这样的
a thousand samples and there was no true difference between the two groups.
两组之间没有真正的差异
That's why the mean is zero.
这是为什么均值等于零的原因
You'll reject the null and conclude that there was a difference if you
如果你测量发现值比这个低 或者比这个高
measure a value less than this one roughly, or greater than this one.
你会拒绝零假设 然后得出结论两者间有差异
So you're probability of falsely concluding there was a difference,
所以你错误地得出两者间有差异的概率
which is often called alpha, is 0.05.
称为 α 为 0.05
If you increase your number of samples, say to 5,000, then the standard error
如果你增加样本量 比如 5000 标准误差会减小
will decrease, so the distribution of results will look much narrower.
结果的分布看上去更窄
To keep alpha the same, that means the cut-offs for
要保持同样的 α 值
rejecting the null will be closer to zero.
就意味着拒绝零假设的临界值接近零
Now let's say you decided to only collect 1,000 page views so
如果你决定只采集 1000 的页面浏览量
that you could make a conclusion more quickly.
这样你可以更快地得出结论
Recall that this is the distribution of results if there is no true difference,
如果没有真正的差异 结果的分布是这样的
and as we saw, alpha will be 0.05.
我们可以看到 α 等于 0.05
Now let's consider the case where there is a difference.
现在让我们来考虑下如果两者间有差异
Specifically, the difference is equal to the practical significance
明确来说 这个差异等于实际显著性
level of 0.02.
为 0.02
You'll fail to reject the null, and
你不能拒绝零假设
conclude there was not a significant difference in the same cases.
然后得出结论 认为没有显著的差异
Now, the probability of failing to reject the null
零假设实际上是错误的 然而却没有拒绝零假设的概率
when the null was in fact false, which is often called Beta, is pretty high.
称为 β 这个值很高
Even if there is a true difference,
就算是真的有差异
it's pretty likely that you'll be inside this range.
很可能也落在这个范围里
So by collecting a small sample, alpha is low,
所以收集少量样本的话 α 比较低
that is, you're unlikely to launch a bad experiment.
也就是说你不太可能进行一个较差的实验
But beta is high, that is, you're likely to fail to launch an experiment that
但是 β 比较高 也就是说很大几率上
actually did have a difference you care about.
你会无法在实验中得到你想要的差异结果
Now beta, or the probability of falsely failing to draw a conclusion,
β 或者说得到错误结论的概率
depends on how big your effect really was.
取决于你的效应有多大
For well behaved distributions like the normal distribution,
对良态的分布例如正态分布来说
as your true change gets larger and larger, then beta will go down.
当变化越来越大 β 会变小
So you typically consider beta at your practical significance boundary
所以一般 β 是在实际显著性边界内
since you don't care about any smaller changes, and
因为你不在意更小的变化
any larger changes will have a lower beta, that is, a lower chance of error.
而变化越大 β 值越小 即误差的几率越小
People also refer to one minus beta as the sensitivity of the experiment.
大家通常将 1 减去 β 视为实验的敏感性
In general, you want your experiment to have a high level of sensitivity at
一般说来 在实际显著性界线内
the practical significance boundary.
你希望实验具有较高的敏感性
People often choose 80%.
大家一般选择 80%
Now again, let's look at what happens if you collect 5,000 samples.
好了 现在来看看如果采集 5000 个样本 会是什么结果
Both distributions get tighter.
两个分布都更加紧密了
And as before, alpha doesn't change.
α 与之前一样 没有变化
However, in the case where there is a true difference,
但是 这里出现了真正的差异
you're much less likely to fall within the range of failing to reject the null.
你无法拒接零假设的几率大大减小了
That is, you're more likely to reject the null and
也就是说 你更有可能拒绝零假设
conclude there was a difference.
并得出两者间有差异的结论
So beta has gone down and your power has increased.
β 减小了 而效应增强了